Ying-Ying Szeto

yingyingszetoo@gmail.com +1 646 421 3288 LinkedIn @yingyingszeto

PORTFOLIO

yingyingszeto.github.io/portfolio

EDUCATION

User Experience Design

Master • Falmouth University Falmouth, UK

Visual and Digital Art

Diploma • Humber College *Toronto, ON, Canada*

SKILLS

Design

UX Strategy
User Research
Interaction Design
Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability Testing
Visual Design

Tools

Figma Miro

Mural

Optimal Workshop HTML/CSS/JS JIRA

LANGUAGE

English Chinese

SUMMARY

UX / Product Designer with over 5+ years of experience. I specialized in end-to-end product design, user research, and concept development. I've shaped Enterprise SaaS and B2B products across industries including insurance, business communications software, and auto marketplace. Authorized to work in the US and does not require sponsorship

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer

Mar 2021 - Aug 2023

Manulife @ Keyteo Consulting • Hong Kong

B2B SaaS • Insurance

- Led end-to-end design for several SaaS applications from concept to completion, impacting 50k+ agents across Hong Kong,
 Vietnam, the Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia
- Partnered closely with cross-functional teams across the entire product lifecycle including Product Managers, Engineers, Operations, and Organizational Leaders
- Leveraged and enhanced internal design systems to drive consistency in product ecosystem

UX/UI Designer

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

M800 • Hong Kong

B2B SaaS • Business Communication

- Transformed the onboarding experience for a b2b product through a simple and delightful design to guide chatbot installation, reducing customer inquiry tickets by 30% in 2 months
- Collaborated with enginners and QAs to push for pixel-perfect production matching the design

UX/UI Designer

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

EAB Systems • Hong Kong

B2B SaaS • Insurance

- Designed and customized user flows and design for client AXA based on the core SaaS product
- Developed design concepts and pitched them to clients from various insurance enterprises

Web Designer

Nov 2015 - Apr 2017

autoTrader.ca • Toronto, ON, Canada

B2C • Automotive marketplace

 Working along side UX and development team to improve the marketplace experience and created delightful graphics

Freelance Designer

2013 - Present

 Designed and developed websites for New Era Cap, Glo, Yuki Spa, and small businesses in Canada and Hong Kong